

EUGENIE UWIMANA

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

PROFIL

I am a junior web developer, flexible with great communication skills. Always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges, after working 8 years in retail, I decided it was time for something new and refreshing. Thanks to my course at Becode, I have learned how to develop static and dynamic web pages using HTML, CSS, JS and PHP. I also have a basic working knowledge of: Git, Bootstrap, MySQL database, NodeJS, Express and MongoDB.

CONTACT

- +32 47 00 17 330
- eugenie11987@gmail.com
- 38 rue du Roetaert 1180 Uccle
- (in) www.linkedin.com/in/e-j-uwimana

SKILLS

Coding Languages:

HTML5 | CSS | JavaScript | PHP

Softwares:

Node.js | Git | VSC | MySQL | PHPmyadmin

Framework:

Bootstrap | Express

LANGUAGES

English | French | Kinyarwanda

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

BeCode, BeCentral, Brussels

2020 - PRESENT

*Creating static & dynamic web pages

*Created a responsive franchise Restaurant webpage

*Created a streaming site in html/css, JavaScript and PHP

*Front & Back-end problem solving.

Gucci - Sales/Visuel Marchandiser

2019 - 2020

Ensure the store is tidy and well run (Presentation, Marchandising).

Christian Louboutin - Sales

2018 - 2018

Welcoming customers giving them advice as well as developing their loyalty.

EDUCATION

BeCode, BeCentral, Brussels

2019 - PRESENT

Web Development Course

London Metropolitan University, London, UK

2006 - 2009

Digital Media Design

HOBBIES

Coding | Traveling | Sports | Cooking | Interior Deco